<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>요기코퍼레이션</title>
    <link>https://yogico.kr/news</link>
    <description>요기코퍼레이션의 최신 소식과 업데이트를 확인하세요.</description>
    <language>ko</language>
    <generator>Custom RSS Feed Generator</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 16:30:00 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 16:30:00 +0900</pubDate>

    <item>
      <title>Yogi Corporation Marks 9th Anniversary with Organizational and Business Restructuring</title>
      <link>https://yogico.kr/news</link>
      <guid>https://yogico.kr/news</guid>
      <description>Yogico's exclusive distributor in Korea, Yogi Corporation, has restructured its organization and business framework on the occasion of its 9th anniversary. Through this restructuring, the company plans to streamline its system into two main divisions.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 15:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yogibo Opens Pop-Up Store at The Hyundai Seoul</title>
      <link>https://yogico.kr/news</link>
      <guid>https://yogico.kr/news</guid>
      <description>Global beanbag icon head Yogibo has opened a pop-up store on the 5th floor of The Hyundai, Seoul. Running from today through the 7th of next month, visitors can try Yogibo products in exhibition and relaxation zones and take part in on-site promotions.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 14:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>"Significant synergies are expected by leveraging Busan Port and Israeli networks."</title>
      <link>https://yogico.kr/news</link>
      <guid>https://yogico.kr/news</guid>
      <description>Yogi Corporation CEO Park Dae-jin said leveraging Busan Port and Israeli networks could create major synergies, arranging bilateral cooperation to expand imports and investment.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 10:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Family Month Concert with HDC Youngchang and Yogibo</title>
      <link>https://yogico.kr/news</link>
      <guid>https://yogico.kr/news</guid>
      <description>HDC Youngchang and Yogibo stage family month event May 16-18, 2025 at Hanam Starfield, showcasing new 2025 Kurzweil pianos with Yogibo relaxation zones, opening day features K-pop and jazz.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 09:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
    </item>

  </channel>
</rss>